<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<document>
  <properties>
    <title>Open-Source Java implementation of the german DTAUS file format</title>
    <author email="cs@jdtaus.org">Christian Schulte</author>
  </properties>
  
  <body>
    <section>
      <p>
        <script type="text/javascript" src="http://pagead2.googlesyndication.com/pagead/show_ads.js" />
      </p>
    </section>
    <section name="Introduction">
      <p>
        jDTAUS provides an implementation of the german DTAUS file format as specified by
        Zentraler Kreditausschuss for the Java platform. Currently it implements the
        DTAUS specification as published on theire website at
        <a href="http://www.zka.de">www.zka.de</a> versioned 2.1 and dated september
        2006. Great care has been taken to fully comply with this specification which
        was one of the goals of this project. A violation to the specification should be
        considered a bug.
      </p>
      <p>
        There is a GUI application available to demonstrate the main features. It is
        distributed using Java-Webstart. You will first have to install the latest
        Java Runtime Environment available at <a href="http://www.java.com">http://www.java.com</a>.
        After downloading and installing Java, the following link will web-start the application.
      </p>
      <p>
        <a href="http://apps.jdtaus.org/jdtaus-editor/launch.jnlp">Web-Start jDTAUS Editor</a>
      </p>
    </section>
    <section name="Releases">
      <p>
        This project uses the central Maven 2 repository to distribute its artifacts.
        Binary releases are available in group <code>org.jdtaus</code>.
      </p>
    </section>
    <section name="Sourcecode">
      <p>
        Currently we do not maintain any source code releases. If you want to build
        yourself you will need to checkout the sources from the project's repository.
        The project's build process is implemented using Maven 2.
        See <a href="http://maven.apache.org">http://maven.apache.org</a> for details.
      </p>
    </section>
    <section name="Support">
      <p>
        It is pretty easy to get support directly from a developer if you need help or
        if you find bugs that need to be reported. Simply write a mail to
        <a href="mailto:support@jdtaus.org">support@jdtaus.org</a>.
        There is a Bugzilla installation at
        <a href="http://bugzilla.jdtaus.org/bugzilla/">http://bugzilla.jdtaus.org/bugzilla/</a>.
        Please browse for possible bugs before reporting.
      </p>
      <p>
        A mailing list is available for public discussion regarding the development
        of the various artifacts. See <a href="mail-lists.html">the lists</a> for
        further information. You may want to sent your code to the jdtaus-users
        mailing list for public review.
      </p>
    </section>
  </body>
</document>
